(Sun Honglei)
(Li Naiwen)
(Guo Jingfei)
(Liu Yuning)
(Gong Jun)
(Chen Xingxu)
(Wang Yuwen)
(Lin Yi)
=Wow The World S2 Extra Episode=
Next, we'll use this game
to warm up your voices.
Let's start with a growl challenge.
Everyone, sing this song with growls.
What's a growl?
How do I even do this?
Who do you think here
can give you a demonstration?
Yuning.
Vocal expert.
Come on.
Alright.
So, a growl sounds like...
Mm.
Good.
Nice.
Such a fierce growl.
It sounds like there is a motorcycle
revving in his throat.
Let's pick our words first.
Which words work best for the growl?
Let's sing "quietly" with a growl.
Let's give it a try, okay?
Okay.
Let's do it.
Set the key.
You set the key.
Three, two, one, go.
♪Summer quietly slips away,
leaving little secrets♪
♪Deep in my heart, deep in my heart♪
♪I can't tell you♪
♪The evening breeze warms my heart♪
♪I think of you again♪
♪So sweet, so sweet♪
♪How could I forget?♪
Good.
Sounds pretty good.
Alright.
Everyone has learned
how to do the growl.
For the next mission,
you'll need to use them.
Our game is called Draw and Guess.
(Draw and Guess)
You'll split into two teams.
Each round, one player from each team
draws the lyrics they see.
Once you're done drawing,
hit the buzzer.
You've got ten seconds to answer
in either a growl or bel canto.
A correct answer scores one point.
If no correct answer within ten seconds,
the turn goes to the other team.
The team with the most correct answers
wins.
Do we draw and guess at the same time?
It's the same song, right?
Yes.
Got it.
Whoever teams up with me will win.
Why?
Because I draw...
I'll team up with you.
(Ride the coattails)
You're good at drawing?
I'm super good at drawing.
I'm pretty good at drawing too.
Let's battle.
Let's draw self-portraits
and see who finishes faster.
Do you dare?
Of course.
Both of you draw Honglei,
okay?
We'll see whose drawing
looks more like him.
Come on.
Let's go.
Go.
Like this?
(Model in position)
(Immersed in drawing)
(Cracking up at his own drawing)
(Taking shape)
Let me tell you.
I'll draw my self-portrait for you guys.
(Show-off time)
I'm drawing really fast.
It actually looks a bit like you.
Impressive.
His drawing is really good.
He's practically a pro.
He could even
set up a street stall.
(I want to check it)
Wait a second.
Wait, look at this one first.
This is his self-portrait.
Let me see.
(Stunned)
Now look at Honglei's portrait.
(Anticipating)
This is you.
(Wow, really hyped up)
Mr. Honglei, please sign your name.
(You didn't spare him either)
(Seeking approval)
My drawing is very vivid, isn't it?
Let me see.
Your drawing
makes me look like a naan
and lamb skewer vendor, doesn't it?
At least, you can tell
this is a human.
Yours...
Honestly, I think mine is better.
I'm super good at drawing.
Guo Jingfei is really good at drawing.
He's quite skilled.
He really draws well.
And he's so fast.
It's
a natural gift.
Come on.
Let's just go with this team setup.
It's fate.
Okay, let's go.
(Round 1 Painters: Chen Xingxu and Guo Jingfei)
Three, two, one.
Here is the question.
(Caged Bird)
(First to start drawing)
(Still reading the prompt)
What is this?
No.
You don't need to know this song.
Just draw
what it describes
Jingfei.
He's almost finished.
(Teammates still waiting)
(Not a still frame)
(Chen Xingxu finishes drawing first)
♪I'm the bird you've caged♪
Caged Bird.
(Correct answer)
(Before it even started)
(It was already over)
Together.
Come on, sing together.
Come on.
Ready, go.
♪I'm the bird you've caged♪
♪I've forgotten how high the sky is♪
♪If I leave the little castle
you've given me♪
♪I don't know who else I could rely on♪
So they won, right?
Yeah.
No big deal.
(Getting ready to go all-out)
Keep it up, Fei.
Alright, next question.
(Secret)
(Waiting eagerly)
Sitting there is so stressful.
Do you feel stressed sitting there?
Right.
Scribbling away furiously.
(Scribbling furiously)
(Creative block hits)
I'm done.
These are eyes.
(Foul)
We can tell they're eyes.
No need to say it.
What's this?
Look Over Here, Girl!
Yes.
Correct.
(Dumbfounded)
(Wow)
(Requesting to review the replay)
- Look left and right, look up and down.
- Okay.
I know. It's
Look Over Here, Girl!
Right.
(Shocked.gif)
My drawing is all about the keywords.
Look.
Awesome.
(Makes no sense)
It's cross-eyed. How did you guess it?
It's not cross-eyed.
It's looking up and looking down.
(So close)
You guessed it.
Good.
You sit in the middle, come on.
You sit in the middle.
You're pretty good.
I got it instantly.
We can figure out Xingxu's drawing too.
(Girl,
Look left and right)
Xingxu's drawing is really good.
We just lost on speed this time.
Lost on speed.
Sorry.
Be faster next round. Come on.
(Drop Tower)
(Anticipating)
Drop Tower.
Correct.
Next question.
(The Girl Under the Streetlamp)
The Girl Under the Streetlamp.
Nice.
(Lei's comfort zone)
Did you guess it?
I really don't know this song.
Ready, go.
♪Beneath that streetlamp light♪
♪A little girl is crying♪
♪Nobody knows where she♪
- Zhou Ye definitely doesn't know it.
- ♪Came from♪
I want to hear Ye's solo version.
(Collective plea for the solo cut)
I want to hear it.
Ye's solo cut.
Zhou Ye's solo cut.
I really don't know how to sing it.
It's fine. They can teach you.
If she can sing after being taught,
that'll do.
♪Beneath that streetlamp light♪
♪A little girl is crying♪
This is a bit hard.
Yuning got totally startled.
Just go for the growl.
Never mind the melody.
Right.
Growl only on the last word,
or the whole line?
Whatever.
Just get one growl out first.
You want growls for the whole line?
♪Beneath that streetlamp light♪
Well...
This doesn't really make sense, does it?
Let's hold our judgment
until we hear the rest.
Hear it first.
♪A little girl is...♪
♪Crying♪
(Ye's singing hack)
Go down. Just remember to go down.
Hold on.
Let's listen again.
♪Nobody knows where she came from♪
You guys...
Do you think that's acceptable?
How dare you question her?
(Six of one VS
Half a dozen of the other)
Alright.
Let them have this one.
She's so good. That takes guts.
This little girl.
If you keep pushing, she'll cry.
Get ready. Next question.
Three, two, one, look.
(Secret)
(Chen Xingxu hits the buzzer first)
Countdown starts now.
- Eight, seven, six,
- Bagel.
five, four,
- Donut.
- three,
- two,
- Sun.
- one,
zero.
Okay.
Our turn.
They are all right.
Bagel.
Donut.
They are all right.
What's it called?
What's that Yang Chaoyue song called?
Burn My Calories.
Right.
Okay.
(So close)
They guessed right.
Let's go.
♪Bye-bye, donuts♪
♪Bubble tea, instant noodles♪
♪Hot pot, rice, and big-plate chicken♪
♪Take them away, don't hold back♪
Perfect.
Pretty good.
Next question.
♪Swaying...♪
Princess. Come on.
Awesome.
Three, two, one, go.
♪Swaying red wine glass♪
♪Lips stained as if with blood♪
♪That unearthly beauty♪
♪An unforgivable sin♪
♪Love truly takes...♪
Courage.
Are we on cheat mode?
(Ridiculously strong)
♪Love truly takes courage♪
♪To face all the gossip and rumors♪
♪One reassuring look from your eyes♪
♪And my love gains its meaning♪
A narrow loss.
Next round, I'm banning Liu Yuning.
(Yuning is scarily good)
Fine.
How about this? Let's switch painters.
Okay.
Who's up?
I'll do it.
(Volunteering)
You go.
Who's drawing this round?
You draw.
I, you...
I...
Lin Yi.
You just focus on drawing. I get you.
With her in this seat, I'm so confident.
From singing to drawing,
they've been competing
their whole lives.
You can't beat me in singing,
(Pre-match trash talk)
and you can't beat me in drawing either.
Just you wait.
(Sparks flying)
It's fine, Lin Yi.
You don't need to draw well.
We get you.
Zhou Ye,
you don't need to draw well either.
We get you.
You don't even have to draw.
You can win by drawing nothing.
(I've got your back)
Just sitting there is enough.
Next question.
(Secret)
Looks like Lin Yi knows it.
Lin Yi, creating is what you do.
Completely lost in his art.
Immersed in his painting.
(Zhou Ye hits the buzzer first)
(Frozen)
(Lost in thought)
Mouse Love Rice?
Balloon.
- This...
- That's a road.
Five, four,
- Balloon.
- three,
- The ball is on its way.
- two...
Sun.
One.
(Still trying)
Don't pick wildflowers by the roadside.
(Make way)
Who is it?
(Key points highlighted)
Cockroach.
Sun Wukong, Wukong.
Iron rod.
I want this iron rod.
Three fights with the White Bone Demon.
You just...
Just guess what this is.
Sun Wukong.
Wukong.
Two.
One.
Time's up.
The Kingdom of Women?
Road.
Where is the road?
(Emergency retracted)
The Broad and Wild Road to Heaven.
Right.
Awesome, Yuning.
Sorry.
(Refusing to face it)
Lin Yi,
explain your creative process.
These are two demons.
Two demons?
This is their soul.
Are these two demons?
Their demonic energy is swirling here.
(Trying to understand)
Demonic energy is swirling here.
And it's been subdued, lying right here.
Like this.
Lin Yi, I think you're
such an interesting person.
I love reading into you.
It's so fun.
You really have to get close to see it.
This is so mind-bending.
Because Lin Yi's drawings
have so many details.
Miss one detail
and you won't figure it out.
Draw it in three strokes or fewer.
(Secret)
This round is in the bag.
Why am I so scared when he goes "ow"?
Every time he says that,
my heart skips a beat.
We're solid.
In the bag.
(Hit the buzzer almost at the same time)
That's not very gentleman-like.
Go ahead.
What is this?
- This is...
- North, south, east, west.
North, south, east, west.
I know.
(Searching the song library)
The north wind...
♪The north wind is blowing♪
Lin Yi, buzz in.
(That's not what I expected at all)
What's this?
You just focus on drawing. I get you.
I get you.
(Don't get it at all)
Cold wind sweeping through.
South.
Is it related to south?
He's under a tree.
Kneeling.
(Completely clueless)
Okay.
Hit the buzzer.
Snow. This is snow.
Right, snow.
(North wind, snow, kneeling)
(Lips sealed tight)
North wind, snow.
- Three, two, one.
- Snowflakes.
(Tried my best)
♪Snowflakes drifting, the north wind...♪
♪Snowflakes drifting♪
One Plum Blossom.
It is Yin Zheng.
Yuan Hua.
(Footage sourced online)
I totally get you.
I figured it out.
Impressive.
Honestly, it's really good.
(Approved by the rival)
Ready, go.
♪Snowflakes drifting,
the north wind whistling alone♪
♪Heaven and earth, all vast and white♪
For the final round,
you can assign the other side's
painter.
Liu Yuning.
Wang Yuwen.
(Round 3
Painters: Wang Yuwen and Liu Yuning)
Next question.
Get ready.
(Invisible Wings)
I...
- Invisible Wings.
♪I know♪
♪I've always
had a pair of invisible wings♪
Wait a second.
I...
(Got totally led astray)
Oh, no. Totally off-key.
Wait.
Get the melody right first.
(Referee Lei is on)
I've got the key.
Follow me.
- Follow you.
- Okay.
(Hold on, God of Song descends)
Ready.
♪I know♪
♪I've always
had a pair of invisible wings♪
♪Lifting me up♪
♪Giving me hope♪
Nice.
Feel the power now?
(Professional team)
Next question.
(Grasshopper's Club Broken Heart)
The phone you are calling
is powered off.
Well...
- Call for Love.
- No.
Grasshopper's Club Broken Heart?
Right.
Come on, let's sing and dance.
♪She always♪
♪Just leaves her phone number♪
♪Never lets me walk her home♪
♪Heard you once fell for her too♪
♪Once just as hopelessly hooked♪
Next question.
Okay.
I think we've got this.
(Scored three straight)
Come on.
(Love Till Death)
Okay.
Ghost.
Obsessed.
I know.
Love Till Death.
His drawing is incredible.
You can see it right away.
(Capturing the essence)
Great work.
♪Even if we die♪
Bring it down a bit first.
(Love Till Death, Bass version)
♪Love even if we die♪
♪Anything less just won't do♪
♪Only this depth of feeling♪
♪Can truly express my love♪
Okay.
Game over.
Congratulations to Honglei, Fei, Yuning,
and Zhou Ye for the win.
The closer the balloon
gets to your face without popping,
the higher your score.
Go.
That's tall enough to fit me.
Is that tall enough for Zhou Ye?
This is actually very simple.
One.
(Who from Earth Group
will complete the challenge?)
Rapid Boarding Dash.
Start.
Quick.
Get in.
That hurts.
Alright, drive.
- Drive.
- Challenge failed.
Such a big gap?
It can't get any faster than this time,
well.
Victory is ours.
Let's go.
(Will the Earth Group pull it off?)
♪Turns out that meeting you♪
♪Is the joy hidden in the world♪
♪We still have to experience together♪
♪Exploring the novelty of the world♪
♪This is our wonderful encounter♪
♪I find good scenery
for you along the way♪
♪You are the joy hidden in the world♪
♪I'm lucky to have met you♪
♪That day,
we traveled together far away♪
♪In countless late nights,
we exchanged courage♪
♪Our fates have already intertwined♪
♪In each other's life trajectories♪
♪We leave behind
bonds like no other for a lifetime♪
♪Turns out that meeting you♪
♪Is the joy hidden in the world♪
♪We still have to experience together♪
♪Exploring the novelty of the world♪
♪This is our wonderful encounter♪
♪I find good scenery
for you along the way♪
♪You are the joy hidden in the world♪
♪I'm lucky to have met you♪
♪Traveling around the earth♪
♪Tasting all the freshness♪
♪Having traveled all corners♪
♪We still stand shoulder to shoulder♪
♪I'm glad to have met you♪
♪We sing beautifully together♪
♪Even if we're scattered in the future♪
♪Thankfully we still share the same sky♪